He's Been Everywhere Mate.
Red Dog is a drama, comedy, family film directed by Kriv Stenders.
The legendary true story of the Red Dog who united a disparate local community while
roaming the Australian outback in search of his long lost master.
John, played by Josh Lucas.
Nancy, played by Rachael Taylor.
Jocko, played by Rohan Nichol.
Tom, played by Luke Ford.
Vanno, played by Arthur Angel.
Peeto, played by John Batchelor.
Red Dog is a 2011 Australian comedy-drama family film written by Daniel Taplitz,
directed by Kriv Stenders and produced by Nelson Woss and Julie Ryan.
It stars Koko as the title character, Josh Lucas,
Rachael Taylor, and John Batchelor.
The film is based on the true story of Red Dog and uses the 2002 novel
Red Dog by Louis de Bernières as the primary source.
At the 2011 Inside Film Awards, Red Dog was nominated in nine
categories and won seven, including best feature film.
The film was also nominated for seven AACTA Awards and won for Best Film.
The film was theatrically released on 4 August
2011 by Roadshow Film Distributors.
The film was followed by a prequel, Red Dog: True Blue released in 2016, and a
spin-off documentary Koko: A Red Dog Story released in 2019.
The film explores themes of australia, 1970s, human animal
relationship, search, based on true story.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.